<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FocusBit</title>
    <link>https://focusbitapp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FocusBit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 21:59:01 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://focusbitapp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with FocusBit on macOS</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/getting-started-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 21:59:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/getting-started-macos/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit installation should be a fast and easy process.
1. Download FocusBit Go to Downloads page and get the version for macOS.

2. Open package and move FocusBit to Applications 
3. Start FocusBit Open Launchpad and find FocusBit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to manage Big tasks with pomodoro technique</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/blog/2019/manage-big-tasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 20:39:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/blog/2019/manage-big-tasks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Big&amp;rdquo; for pomodoro is anything that does not fit into the standard 25 minutes. In practice it appears that almost all tasks initially are &amp;ldquo;Big&amp;rdquo;. Typically you would &amp;ldquo;divide and conquer&amp;rdquo; such things but this only works when the scope of the task is known ahead. So how to tackle it when it&amp;rsquo;s not?
Make a plan to make a plan Usually what I do is I start a reasonably small pomodoro timer for just making a plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to accomplish things you&#39;re not interested in</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/blog/2019/accomplish-things-not-interested-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 20:26:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/blog/2019/accomplish-things-not-interested-in/</guid>
      <description>Motivation is a great thing. It helps to move mountains, make lemonade from the apples or build the snowman out of rain. Also it helps to perform your daily job. But when it&amp;rsquo;s gone, even Chuck Norris cannot help you to bring it back. The problem is that it can be gone in the middle of the day leaving you with a pile of work that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to do but you have to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with FocusBit on Windows</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/getting-started-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 18:59:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/getting-started-windows/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit installation should be a fast and easy process.
1. Download FocusBit Go to Downloads page and get the version for Windows.

2. Extract archive Right-click the archive and select &amp;ldquo;Extract All&amp;rdquo;

Select destination and press &amp;ldquo;Extract&amp;rdquo;

3. Open FocusBit Find file &amp;ldquo;FocusBit.exe&amp;rdquo; and double-click it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using pomodoro technique with FocusBit</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/blog/2019/pomodoro-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 08:45:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/blog/2019/pomodoro-technique/</guid>
      <description>What is the Pomodoro technique? Pomodoro is a time management technique for improving productivity. It was developed in Italy in 80s. It breaks down work into smaller tasks that can be done in 25-minute intervals, separated by short 5-minute breaks. During 25 minutes interval (called &amp;ldquo;pomodoro&amp;rdquo;) you should only work on the task you decided. In other words you should postpone checking social media and emails for when the break starts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with FocusBit on Linux</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/getting-started-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 18:59:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/getting-started-linux/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit installation should be a fast and easy process.
1. Download FocusBit Go to Downloads page and get the version for Linux.

2. Allow Execution as a Program Right-click the AppImage file and select &amp;ldquo;Properties&amp;rdquo;

Check the checkbox &amp;ldquo;Allow this file to run as a program&amp;rdquo; (this might be different in your desktop environment)

3. Open FocusBit Double-click AppImage file - you&amp;rsquo;re good to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/buy/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit License $4.99 USD Price in USD. VAT may apply.  &amp;nbsp; Buy Now!     Is there a subscription? No, there is no subscription or recurring charge. You are only charged a one-time fee to use the product.
 Is my data private? FocusBit does not collect any private data or telemetry. You don&#39;t need to register an online account. You can read more about privacy here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/download/</guid>
      <description>   FocusBit for macOS Free 14-day trial. Buy for $4.99. Learn more
Download        FocusBit for Windows Free 14-day trial. Buy for $4.99. Learn more
Download        FocusBit for Linux Free 14-day trial. Buy for $4.99. Learn more
Download      What&#39;s new:  Done list to track past work Notifications in tray and taskbar Ability to scroll in timer setup fields Context menu to manage todo tasks Animate tray icon during the work interval   Getting started On Windows On macOS On Linux &amp;nbsp; Other downloads: FocusBit for Windows FocusBit for macOS FocusBit for Linux    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensing</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/licensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/licensing/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit for macOS, Windows and for Linux are separate applications.
On all platforms we support a free 2 week trial to allow you fully test FocusBit. The trial ends automatically and at the end you can decide if you want to purchase a license.
License is valid both for all versions of the application so you can enjoy using FocusBit everywhere.
Prices for FocusBit may be different in your currency. In order to see how much it costs locally you have to start buying a license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit does not store or process any personal data. Desktop application does not collect telemetry. All payments on this website are processed by Paddle and are regulated by Paddle privacy policy and Paddle terms of use.
FocuBit is an offline-first software. We do not offer cloud syncronization or online accounts. All data stays on your local machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/support/</guid>
      <description>     We’re here to help you out     document.getElementById(&#39;forum_embed&#39;).src = &#39;https://groups.google.com/forum/embed/?place=forum/focusbit-support&#39; + &#39;&amp;showsearch=true&amp;showpopout=true&amp;showtabs=false&#39; + &#39;&amp;parenturl=&#39; + encodeURIComponent(window.location.href);    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>