<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xpiks is a free and open source keywording and uploading tool on FocusBit</title>
    <link>https://focusbitapp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Xpiks is a free and open source keywording and uploading tool on FocusBit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://focusbitapp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/about/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit is created by Taras Kushnir (that&amp;rsquo;s me 👋). I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer, architect and mentor.
I&amp;rsquo;m a big GTD believer and creating and using FocusBit personally helped me a lot. After I experienced magic of being able to concentrate I decided to share it with others.
If you have a support request please visit Support. Otherwise I will be happy to hear from your at hello@focusbit.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/buy/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit License $4.99 USD Price in USD. VAT may apply.  &amp;nbsp; Buy Now!     Is there a subscription? No, there is no subscription or recurring charge. You are only charged a one-time fee to use the product.
 Is my data private? FocusBit does not collect any private data or telemetry. You don&#39;t need to register an online account. You can read more about privacy here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/download/</guid>
      <description>   FocusBit for macOS Free 14-day trial. Buy for $4.99. Learn more
Download        FocusBit for Windows Free 14-day trial. Buy for $4.99. Learn more
Download        FocusBit for Linux Free 14-day trial. Buy for $4.99. Learn more
Download      What&#39;s new:  Done list to track past work Notifications in tray and taskbar Ability to scroll in timer setup fields Context menu to manage todo tasks Animate tray icon during the work interval   Getting started On Windows On macOS On Linux &amp;nbsp; Other downloads: FocusBit for Windows FocusBit for macOS FocusBit for Linux    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensing</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/licensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/licensing/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit for macOS, Windows and for Linux are separate applications.
On all platforms we support a free 2 week trial to allow you fully test FocusBit. The trial ends automatically and at the end you can decide if you want to purchase a license.
License is valid for all versions of the application so you can enjoy using FocusBit everywhere.
Prices for FocusBit may be different in your currency. In order to see how much it costs locally you have to start buying a license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>FocusBit does not store or process any personal data. Desktop application does not collect telemetry. All payments on this website are processed by Paddle and are regulated by Paddle privacy policy and Paddle terms of use.
FocuBit is an offline-first software. We do not offer cloud syncronization or online accounts. All data stays on your local machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://focusbitapp.com/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focusbitapp.com/support/</guid>
      <description>     We’re here to help you out You can also post to this group by mailing hello@focusbit.com
    document.getElementById(&#39;forum_embed&#39;).src = &#39;https://groups.google.com/forum/embed/?place=forum/focusbit-support&#39; + &#39;&amp;showsearch=true&amp;showpopout=true&amp;showtabs=false&#39; + &#39;&amp;parenturl=&#39; + encodeURIComponent(window.location.href);    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>